<IssueSpecification version="4">
    <Name>
        <en>Demo INZ Emailer E-mail</en>
        <nl>Demo INZ Emailer E-mail</nl>
    </Name>
    <ShortName>
        <en>E-mail</en>
        <nl>E-mail</nl>
    </ShortName>
    <SchemeManager>irma-demo</SchemeManager>
    <IssuerID>inz-emailer</IssuerID>
    <CredentialID>email</CredentialID>
    <Description>
        <en>E-mail</en>
        <nl>E-mail</nl>
    </Description>
    <ShouldBeSingleton>false</ShouldBeSingleton>
    <IssueURL>
        <en>https://demo.irma.nz</en>
        <nl>https://demo.irma.nz</nl>
    </IssueURL>
    <Category>
        <en>Personal</en>
        <nl>Persoonlijk</nl>
    </Category>
    <FAQIntro>
        <en>Add your email address to your IRMA app. You can add multiple email addresses.</en>
        <nl>Laad je e-mailadres in je IRMA-app. Je kunt meerdere e-mailadressen toevoegen.</nl>
    </FAQIntro>
    <FAQPurpose>
        <en>With your email address in your IRMA app, you can show that this address is really yours. For instance, you
            can use your email address to fill in a line in a form, or to login at a website.
        </en>
        <nl>Met jouw e-mailadres in de IRMA-app kun je laten zien dat dit adres echt bij jou hoort. Je kunt bijvoorbeeld
            je e-mailadres gebruiken om een regel in een formulier in te vullen of om op een website in te loggen.
        </nl>
    </FAQPurpose>
    <FAQContent>
        <en>You will add the following data.\n• emailaddress\n• email domain name</en>
        <nl>Je laadt de volgende gegevens.\n• e-mailadres\n• e-mail domeinnaam</nl>
    </FAQContent>
    <FAQHowto>
        <en>Complete the following steps.\n1. Enter your e-mail address.\n2. Open your email application and go to your
            Inbox (if there is no new mail soon, please check your Spam folder).\n3. Click the link in the email
            message, sent by the Privacy by Design Foundation. If you see a QR code on your computer screen, scan it
            with the QR scanner in your IRMA app. The Privacy by Design Foundation copies your email data into your IRMA
            app.\n\nYou now receive a card with your email address and its domain name in your IRMA app. Repeat this
            process for other email addresses that you wish to add.
        </en>
        <nl>Doorloop de volgende stappen.\n1. Vul je e-mailadres in.\n2. Open je e-maillezer en ga naar 'inkomende
            berichten' (als er geen mail verschijnt, controleer zonodig je Spam folder).\n3. Open de link in het
            e-mailbericht van de stichting Privacy by Design. Als je een QR-code te zien krijgt, scan deze met je
            IRMA-app. De stichting Privacy by Design voegt je e-mail gegevens toe in je IRMA-app.\n\nJe ontvangt nu een
            kaartje met je e-mailadres en de domeinnaam van dat adres in je IRMA app. Herhaal dit proces voor ieder
            e-mail adres dat je toe wil voegen.
        </nl>
    </FAQHowto>
    <Attributes>
        <Attribute id="email">
            <Name>
                <en>User e-mail address</en>
                <nl>E-mailadres</nl>
            </Name>
            <Description>
                <en>Your verified e-mail address</en>
                <nl>Je geverifieerde e-mailadres</nl>
            </Description>
        </Attribute>
    </Attributes>
</IssueSpecification>
